<?xml version="1.0"?>
<news>
	<news_item>
		<date>July 16. 2011</date>
		<title>NYSH at the New York City Grand National Tournament, New York, NY</title>
		<text>NYSH came out firing in their first game of the day against #1 seed Panik Attack,avenging they DCKO loss with a 6-2 victory.  The Hammers kept rolling handing 8-4 and 4-2 defeats to top ranked teams OSC and The Situation, respectively.  Moving into elimination NYSH faced The Angry Penguins from Boston.  The Penguins got some offense going in the first, loading the bases and scoring one, but ultimately the blue offense was too much to handle and NYSH won a 10-1 decision. The quarter-finals found NYSH matched up against higher seeded availables team Poison iV.  This hard fought defensive battle left NYSH on top 2-1.  The ride would end in the semi-finals where NYSH was vexed by OSC's airtight defense and brutal pitching 0-2, but not before pitcher Karl Pawlewicz fouled out 3 consecutive batters in one of the most dominant pitching performances in kickball history.</text>
		<pic>../news_pics/nycgn2011.png</pic>
	</news_item>
	<news_item>
		<date>July 16. 2011</date>
		<title>NYSH at K365 Open, Washington DC</title>
		<text>NYSH opened the day with a 10-0 victory over DC's BLTN All-Stars.  Things got tough against up and coming squad Blood Sweat and Beers who handed the Hammers a 6-2 defeat, fueled by a 2 out grand slam.  NYSH turned things around defeating Emperor's Club 7-1 and Back in Black 5-3 but a high runs against total assured NYSH a tough see in elims.  NYSH would face the number 1 ranked Circuit squad Panik Attack in the round of 16 and while the Hammers were able to generate some offense, they could not get enough runs across, nor hold off a surging PA and fell 6-2.</text>
		<pic>../news_pics/dcko2011.png</pic>
	</news_item>
	<news_item>
		<date>May 21. 2011</date>
		<title>NYSH at Virginia Beach Kickball Open, Virginia Beach, VA</title>
		<text>Once again featured in the pool of death, NYSH battled hard for ties against The Situation, Inglorious Basterds and Back in Black, earing a win over Emperor's Club.  NYSH would advance to face perennial title contender OSC in the first round of elimination. After a tight battle, NYSH prevailed, advancing to the tournament semi-finals against #3 in the nation Fully Loaded.  NYSH would eventually fall short of a finals berth by a score of 2-1, but VBKO was another step forward for the new team in blue and heralds great things to come. </text>
		<pic>../news_pics/vbko2011.png</pic>
	</news_item>
	<news_item>
		<date>May 7, 2011</date>
		<title>NYSH Wins Connecticut Kickball Open, Hartford, CT</title>
		<text>Hostile weather and old tyme baseball players could not deter The Shower Hammers, who plowed through the comptetition, earning their first tournament victory in only their second tournament as a team.  During pool play, NYSH handily dispatched IJTI2, FURM, Nailed at the Plate and Sorry for Partying, advancing to take wins over Nailed and Sorry for Partying in elimination.  Revenge was sweet. </text>
		<pic>../news_pics/cko2011.png</pic>
	</news_item>
	<news_item>
		<date>February 19, 2011</date>
		<title>NYSH at South Florida Kickball Open, Ft. Lauderdate, FL.</title>
		<text> NYSH's first tournament together was true test of a yourng team's mettle.  The first game of the day was a grueling battle against the vaunted Situation from Virginia Beach.  This was a defensive battle that ended in a 0-0 tie, but more importantly it was in this game that star outfielder Kelly Wildeman went down with a torn ligament in her knee. Fan and clutch sub Madeline Schwab stepped in to keep NYSH on the field.  In the second pool play game, NYSH dropped a squeaker to top 5 ranked Ft. Lauderdale club Balls Deeper.  NYSH bounced back in the second half of pool play defeating Chicken it For Ghana and Miami's Showtime.  NYSH rolled into elimination and faced off against cross town rival Lock it Up.  The orange team deftly picked apart NYSHs defense and exploited several strategic mistakes by the kids im blue posting a 9-4 beating.  Defeated but unbowed, NYSH, hit the beach and then went back to lab, where they would dissect their mistakes and grow stronger. </text>
		<pic>../news_pics/sfko2011.png</pic>
	</news_item>
	
	
</news>